[{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665708929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":38496,"timeElapsed":1733156},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665721072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":12141,"timeElapsed":1745298},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665745567,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":24495,"timeElapsed":1769794},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665751703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":6135,"timeElapsed":1775930},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665769664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":17959,"timeElapsed":1793891},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665777930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":8264,"timeElapsed":1802156},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665783113,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":5182,"timeElapsed":1807340},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665792129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":9014,"timeElapsed":1816356},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665832347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":40216,"timeElapsed":1856574},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665894642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":61127,"timeElapsed":1918869},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665906778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":12135,"timeElapsed":1931005},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665925316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":18537,"timeElapsed":1949543},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665929530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":4213,"timeElapsed":1953757},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665935786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":6255,"timeElapsed":1960013},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665943059,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":7271,"timeElapsed":1967286},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665948379,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":5319,"timeElapsed":1972606},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665956452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":8072,"timeElapsed":1980679},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665959915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3462,"timeElapsed":1984142},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665976755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":15839,"timeElapsed":2000982},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665985917,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":9160,"timeElapsed":2010144},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665994155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":8238,"timeElapsed":2018382},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665999563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5407,"timeElapsed":2023790},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666004540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4975,"timeElapsed":2028767},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666008940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":4399,"timeElapsed":2033167},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666012388,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3447,"timeElapsed":2036615},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666018397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6008,"timeElapsed":2042624},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666025060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6662,"timeElapsed":2049287},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666039548,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":13446,"timeElapsed":2063775},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666048180,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":8631,"timeElapsed":2072407},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666052341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4160,"timeElapsed":2076568},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666059021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":6679,"timeElapsed":2083248},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666063077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4054,"timeElapsed":2087304},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666070454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7376,"timeElapsed":2094681},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666074821,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":4366,"timeElapsed":2099048},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666084541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":9719,"timeElapsed":2108768},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666089717,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"221","question":"What magical ability (for example, reading minds, teleporting, invisibility) would you want to have and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":5175,"timeElapsed":2113944},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666143599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":52856,"timeElapsed":2167826},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666147519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3918,"timeElapsed":2171746},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666156079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":8559,"timeElapsed":2180306},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666158991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":2911,"timeElapsed":2183218},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666163895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":4903,"timeElapsed":2188122},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666173158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":9262,"timeElapsed":2197385},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666178102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4943,"timeElapsed":2202329},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666186328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":8223,"timeElapsed":2210554},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666189649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3320,"timeElapsed":2213876},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666219127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":28567,"timeElapsed":2243354},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666230399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":11271,"timeElapsed":2254626},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666234936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4536,"timeElapsed":2259163},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666238640,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3703,"timeElapsed":2262867},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666245609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6967,"timeElapsed":2269836},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666248552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2943,"timeElapsed":2272779},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666251840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3287,"timeElapsed":2276067},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666259641,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":7800,"timeElapsed":2283868},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666263921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4279,"timeElapsed":2288148},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666308066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":43351,"timeElapsed":2332293},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666314026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5959,"timeElapsed":2338253},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666325690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":11663,"timeElapsed":2349917},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666341594,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":15904,"timeElapsed":2365821},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666350842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":9246,"timeElapsed":2375069},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666360185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":9343,"timeElapsed":2384412},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666365003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4815,"timeElapsed":2389229},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666368371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3368,"timeElapsed":2392598},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666402691,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":34318,"timeElapsed":2426917},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666409907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"135","question":"What was the best gift you ever received and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":7215,"timeElapsed":2434134},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666421019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":9950,"timeElapsed":2445246},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666425203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":4182,"timeElapsed":2449430},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666428476,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3272,"timeElapsed":2452703},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666431285,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2807,"timeElapsed":2455512},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666437156,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":5870,"timeElapsed":2461383},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666439556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2399,"timeElapsed":2463783},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666444228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":4672,"timeElapsed":2468455},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666449380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":5151,"timeElapsed":2473607},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666466596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"189","question":"What was the first car you owned or drove regularly? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":17215,"timeElapsed":2490823},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666481693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":14096,"timeElapsed":2505920},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666488653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6958,"timeElapsed":2512879},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666493349,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":4695,"timeElapsed":2517576},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666495470,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2120,"timeElapsed":2519697},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666501221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":5750,"timeElapsed":2525448},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666504486,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3264,"timeElapsed":2528713},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666508077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3591,"timeElapsed":2532304},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666512973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4895,"timeElapsed":2537200},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666519573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":6598,"timeElapsed":2543800},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666521789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2215,"timeElapsed":2546016},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666534949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":12488,"timeElapsed":2559176},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666538445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3495,"timeElapsed":2562672},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666547021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8574,"timeElapsed":2571248},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666550189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3167,"timeElapsed":2574416},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666553606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3415,"timeElapsed":2577833},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666556910,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3304,"timeElapsed":2581137},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666563990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":7078,"timeElapsed":2588217},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666572206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":8215,"timeElapsed":2596433},{"subjectID":"eeaq675fy9","prolificID":"5cd063ce657e300016f6c95a","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742161dadbbddbd767a8c1","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666575423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"53","question":"What do you think makes somebody a good parent or caretaker?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3216,"timeElapsed":2599650}]